Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
- Series I: Pacific Ocean
  - Group 04 - Pacific Ocean Precision Depth Recordings, 17688999
    - 0031.2 [Multiple Profiles Along South American Continental Margin] (Folder Barcode: 00275671228)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Profiles: 52, 54 and 55 (Baird); 53 and 59 (Horizon); 56-58 (Vema 15). Sheet No. 8, 3 August 1961.
    - 0031.3 [Multiple Profiles Along South American Continental Margin] (Folder Barcode: 00275671228)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Profiles: 60, 62, 65 and 66 (Vema 17); 61 and 64 (Vema 15); 63 (Baird). Sheet No. 9.
    - 0031.4 [Multiple Profiles Along South American Continental Margin] (Folder Barcode: 00275671228)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Profiles: 67 and 71 (Vema 17); 68- 70, 72 and 73 (Vema 15). Sheet No. 10.
    - 0031.5 [Multiple Profiles Along South American Continental Margin] (Folder Barcode: 00275671228)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Profiles: 74 and 75 (Discovery II); 76 and 77 (Vema 17); 88 (Vema 16); 79 (Meteor); and 80 (Capt. Canepa). Sheet No. 11.
    - 0031.6 [Index to Multiple Profiles In Gulf of Panama] (Folder Barcode: 00275671216)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 2˚ to 10˚ North and 77˚ to 85˚ West. Profile tracks 1-9 in Gulf of Panama. Publication graphic.
    - 0031.7 [Index to Multiple Profiles In Gulf of Panama and Along West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275671216)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 12˚ South to 10˚ North and 77˚ to 87˚ West. Profile tracks 1-25 in Gulf of Panama and along west coast of South America. Publication graphic.
    - 0031.8 [Index to Multiple Profiles Along West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275671216)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 12˚ South to 3˚ North and 77˚ to 87˚ West. Profile tracks 10-25 along west coast of South America. Publication graphic.
    - 0031.9 [Index to Multiple Profiles Along West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275671216)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 10˚ to 27˚ South and 70˚ to 82˚ West. Profile tracks 24-49 along west coast of South America. Publication graphic.
    - 0032 [Multiple Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671162)
      a. Film negative b. Profiles 1 - 23. Signed by Marie Tharp
    - 0033 [Multiple Profiles Off New Zealand] (Folder Barcode: 00275671162)
      a. Tracing paper b. Profiles 1 - 23. Signed by Marie Tharp.
    - 0034 [Multiple Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671162)
      a. Film negative b. Profiles 1 - 24. Signed by Marie Tharp.
    - 0035 [Multiple Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671162)
      a. Ozalid. b. Profiles 1 - 24. Signed by Marie Tharp.
    - 0036 [Pacific Ocean Profile Originating from Pt. Reyes California] (Folder Barcode: 00275671162)
      a. Graph paper b. Nautical miles from Point Reyes, California
    - 0037 [Pacific Ocean Profile] (Folder Barcode: 00275671162)
    - 0038 [Profiles Off the Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275671198)
      a. Film negative b. From 30˚ to 65˚ South and 70˚ to 150˚ West. Displays topographic data plotted perpendicular to the ship tracks in corrected meters. Fracture zones are indicated by dashed lines. Magnetic anomalies are indicated by stripped patterns.
    - 0039 Pacific Ocean Worksheet - Profiles and Physiography (Folder Barcode: 00275671198)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Profiles A thru G shown.
    - 0040 [Profiles of the Southeast Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275671198)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West. Tracks with profiles plotted with selected soundings.
    - 0041 Point Reyes to Oahu - Route 'A' (Folder Barcode: 00275671198)
      a. Linen
    - 0042 Point Reyes to Oahu - Route I (Folder Barcode: 00275671198)
    - 0043 [Multiple Profiles of the Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275671198)
      a. Tracing paper b. Profiles 1 - 19 shown.
    - 0044 [Multiple Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671186)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Profiles 1 - 11 shown.
    - 0045 [Multiple Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671186)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Profiles 12 - 17 shown.
    - 0046 [Multiple Pacific Ocean Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671186)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Walvis Ridge, Rockall Ridge, Madagascar, Carnegie Ridge, Nasca Ridge and Iquique Ridges shown.
    - 0047 [Tracings of Topographic Profiles Between Nasco and Iqueque] (Folder Barcode: 00275671186)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Four profiles shown.
    - 0048 [Summary Worksheet of Profiles Across the Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275671174, 00275671174)
      a. Tracing paper b. Notes: "The original profiles were plotted at 100:1 and were 20 inches wide. These profiles have been correlated peak for peak, lined up and shot down in size to this composite worksheet. This is a negative of a worksheet (the original was much larger). The finished, inked drawing for publication will probably be in the Pacific ocean bin. Twenty five profiles lined up to work with 170˚ East and 60˚ South across the Mid- Oceanic Ridge in the southeast Pacific Ocean."
    - 0049 [Miscellaneous Pacific Ocean Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671174, 00275671174)
      a. Frosted acetate
    - 0050 [Eltanin Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671174, 00275671174)
      a. Tracing paper b. Four profiles across the New Zealand Plateau, five profiles across the Mid-Oceanic Ridge, and four profiles across the Chile Ridge.
    - 0051 [Vema 2 Profiles #343- #363] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0052 [Vema 2 Profiles #366a - #379] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0053 [Vema 2 Profiles #380 - #397] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0054 [Vema 2 Profiles #398 - #415] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0055 [Vema 2 Profiles #419 - #433] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0056 [Vema 2 Profiles #440 - #447] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0057 [Vema 2 Profiles #454 - #461] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0058 [Vema 2 Profiles #468 - #478] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0059 [Vema 2 Profiles #482 - #489] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0060 [Vema 2 Profiles #496 - #512] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
    - 0061 [Vema 2 Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671083)
      a. Negative print. b. Shows profiles C-1 thru C-6
    - 0062 [Vema 2 Profile #786] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile C-1
    - 0063 [Vema 2 Profiles #787 - #791] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile C-2
    - 0064 [Vema 2 Profiles #792 - #797] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile C-3
    - 0065 [Vema 2 Profiles #798 - #803] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile C-4
    - 0066 [Vema 2 Profiles #804 - #809] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile C-5
    - 0067 [Vema 2 Profiles #810 - #815] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile C-6
    - 0068 [Vema 2 Profiles #8?? - #820] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A, 0027564772A)
    - 0069 [Vema 2 Profiles #850 - #856] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
    - 0070 [Vema 2 Profiles #857 - #862] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
    - 0071 [Vema 2 Profiles #864 - #870] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
    - 0072 [Vema 2 Profiles #871 - #877] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
    - 0073 [Vema 2 Profiles #878 - #882] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
    - 0074 [Vema 2 Profiles #850 - #877] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
      a. Positive print b. Photographic reductions of Vema 2 #850 - #877
    - 0075 [Vema 2 Profiles #949 - #954] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
    - 0076 [Vema 2 Profiles #955 - #062] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071, 0027564772A)
    - 0077 [Vema 2 Profiles #063 - #969] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071)
    - 0078 [Vema 2 Profiles #970 - #975] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071)
    - 0079 [Vema 2 Profiles #976 - #981] (Folder Barcode: 00275671071)
    - 0080 [Vema 2 Profiles #982 - #987] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0081 [Vema 2 Profiles #988 - #993] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0082 [Vema 2 Profiles #994 - #999] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0083 [Vema 2 Profiles #1001 - #1006] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647718)
    - 0084 [Vema 2 Profiles #1008 - #1013] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647718)
    - 0085 [Vema 2 Profiles #1014 - #1019] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647706)
    - 0086 [Vema 2 Profiles #1020 - #1028] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0087 [Vema 2 Profiles #1029 - #1034] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0088 [Vema 2 Profiles #1035 - #1040] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0089 [Vema 2 Profiles #1041- #1046] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0090 [Vema 2 Profiles #1047 - #1052] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0091 [Vema 2 Profiles #1053 - #1058] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0092 [Vema 2 Profiles #1059 - #1064] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0093 [Vema 2 Profiles #1065 - #1071] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0094 [Vema 2 Profiles #1072 - #1078] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647706)
    - 0095 [Vema 2 Profiles #1079 - #1084] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A)
    - 0096 [Vema 2 Profiles #1085 - #1089] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647706)
    - 0097 [Vema 2 Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647706)
      a. Negative print. b. Shows profiles A-1, A-2, A-8 thru A-12
    - 0098 [Vema 2 Profiles #1081 - #1089] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647706)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile A-1
    - 0099 [Vema 2 Profiles #1079 - #1080] (Folder Barcode: 0027567106A, 00275647706)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile A-2
    - 0100 [Vema 2 Profiles #1020 - #1022] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile A-8
    - 0101 [Vema 2 Profiles #1010 - #1019] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile A-9
    - 0102 [Vema 2 Profile] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile A-10
    - 0103 [Vema 2 Profiles #982 - #993] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile A-11
    - 0104 [Vema 2 Profiles #980 - #970] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile A-12
    - 0105 [Vema 2 Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Shows profiles B-3 thru B-6, B-13 thru B-14.
    - 0106 [Vema 2 Profiles #1065 - #1077] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile B-3
    - 0107 [Vema 2 Profiles #1054 - #1064] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile B-4
    - 0108 [Vema 2 Profiles #1041 - #1052]` (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile B-5
    - 0109 [Vema 2 Profiles #1029 - #1040] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile B-6
    - 0110 [Vema 2 Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile B-13
    - 0111 [Vema 2 Profiles #949 - #951] (Folder Barcode: 00275671058, 0027564769A)
      a. Negative print. b. Profile B-14
    - 0112 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 0027564769A, 00275671046)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 1, 11 June 1969
    - 0113 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 0027564769A, 00275671046)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 1, 12 June 1969
    - 0114 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671046)
    - 0115 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671046)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 1, 13 June 1969
    - 0116 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671046)
    - 0117 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671046)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 1, 15 June 1969
    - 0118 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671046)
      a. Film negative b. End air gun record No. 2, 16 June 1969
    - 0119 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671046)
      a. Film negative b. Begin air gun record No. 4, 23 June 1969
    - 0120 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
      a. Film negative b. Begin air gun record No. 4, 23/24 June 1969
    - 0121 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
      a. Film negative b. Begin air gun record No. 4, 25 June 1969
    - 0122 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034, 00275647688)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 5, 26/27 June 1969
    - 0123 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 5, 27 June 1969
    - 0124 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
    - 0125 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 5, 28 June 1969
    - 0126 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
    - 0127 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
    - 0128 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 5, 30 June 1969
    - 0129 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671034)
      a. Film negative b. Begin air gun record No. 6, 1/2 July 1969
    - 0130 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
    - 0131 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
      a. Film negative b. Begin air gun record No. 7, 4 July 1969
    - 0132 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
    - 0133 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
    - 0134 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
      a. Film negative b. Begin air gun record No. 7, 8 July 1969
    - 0135 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 8, 11 July 1969
    - 0136 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 8, 12 July 1969
    - 0137 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 8, 12/13 July 1969
    - 0138 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
    - 0139 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671150)
      a. Film negative b. Begin air gun record No. 10, 19 July 1969
    - 0140 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative b. End of air gun record No. 10, 20 July 1969
    - 0141 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative b. Begin of air gun record No. 11, 20 July 1969
    - 0142 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative b. Air gun record No. 11, 21 July 1969
    - 0143 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative b. End of air gun record No. 11, 21 July 1969
    - 0144 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative b. End of air gun record No. 12, 23 July 1969
    - 0145 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative b. Begin of air gun record No. 13, 25 July 1969
    - 0146 [Glomar Challenger - Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative b. End of air gun record No. 13, 28 July 1969
    - 0147 [Miscellaneous Profile] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
      a. Film negative
    - 0148 [Profile #765] (Folder Barcode: 00275671149)
    - 0149 [Profile #800] (Folder Barcode: 00275647688, 00275671149)
    - 0150 [Profile #825] (Folder Barcode: 00275647688, 00275671149)
    - 0151 [Profile #875] (Folder Barcode: 00275647688, 00275671149)
    - 0152 [H.M.N.Z.S Endeavor and Wilhoite Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671137, 00275647676)
      a. Paper. b. Profiles A thru F, over the Campbell Plateau, 1965
    - 0153 [Endeavor Profile A] (Folder Barcode: 00275671137, 00275647676)
      a. Film positive b. Covers Auckland Islands and Cathedral Banks
    - 0154 [Wilhoite Profile B] (Folder Barcode: 00275671137, 00275647676)
      a. Film positive b. Covers Pukaki Rise, Campbell Islands Shelf and the Sub Antarctic Slope
    - 0155 [Endeavor Profile C] (Folder Barcode: 00275671137, 00275647676)
    - 0156 [Endeavor Profiles D, E, and F] (Folder Barcode: 00275671137, 00275647676)
      a. Film positive b. Covers Pukaki Rise, Campbell Islands Shelf, Bounty Platform and the Sub Antarctic Slope. 1965
    - 0157 [Endeavor Profile E] (Folder Barcode: 00275671137, 00275647676)
      a. Film negative b. Covers the Campbell Plateau, the Sub Antarctic Slope and the Southwest Pacific Basin.
    - 0158 [Endeavor Profile F] (Folder Barcode: 00275671137, 00275647676)
      a. Film negative b. Covers the Bounty Platform, the Sub Antarctic Slope and the Southwestern Pacific Basin.
    - 0159 [Endeavor and Wilhoite Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275647676, 00275671125)
      a. Film positive b. Endeavor profile A covers the Campbell Plateau, Cathedral Depression and the Auckland Slope. Endeavor profile C covers the Campbell Plateau the Sub Antarctic Slope, the Southwestern Pacific Basin and a Seamount. Endeavor D profile covers the Campbell Plateau and the Endeavor Banks. Wilhoite profile covers the Campbell Plateau, the Sub Antarctic Slope and the Southwestern Pacific Basin.
    - 0160 [Pukaki, Endeavor and Taranui Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275647676, 00275671125)
      a. Paper. b. Profiles A and B (Pukaki), C and D (Endeavor), and E (Taranui)
    - 0161 [Endeavor and Pukaki Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125,00275647664)
      a. Film negative b. Four profiles showing Campbell Plateau, Snares Depression and the Auckland Islands Shelf.
    - 0162 [Endeavor and Pukaki Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125, 00275647664)
      a. Film positive b. Five profiles showing Campbell Plateau, Snares Depression and the Auckland Islands Shelf.
    - 0163 [Endeavor Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125, 00275647664)
      a. Paper. b. Eight profiles showing Antipodes Islands, Bounty Platform and the Pukaki Saddle
    - 0164 [Endeavor Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125, 00275647664)
      a. Film positive b. Eight profiles showing Antipodes Islands, Bounty Platform and the Pukaki Saddle
    - 0165 [Endeavor Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125, 00275647664)
      a. Film negative b. Eight profiles showing Antipodes Islands, Bounty Platform and the Pukaki Saddle
    - 0166 [Endeavor Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125, 00275647664)
      a. Paper. b. Profile A shows Macquarie Ridge, the Emerald Basin and the Auckland Slopes.
    - 0167 [Endeavor Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125, 00275647664)
      a. Film positive b. Profile A shows Macquarie Ridge, the Emerald Basin and the Auckland Slopes.
    - 0168 [Endeavor and Glacier Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125)
      a. Paper. b. Profiles A thru D cover the Auckland Slopes
    - 0169 [Endeavor Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671125)
      a. Film negative b. Profiles A, B and C cover the Auckland Slopes
    - 0170 [Endeavor and Glacier Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Film positive b. Profiles A, B, C and D cover the Auckland Slopes
    - 0171 [Abyssal Hill Province Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Paper. b. Four profiles shown
    - 0172 [Abyssal Hill Province Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Film positive b. Two profiles (A and B) covering the Abyssal Hill Province shown.
    - 0173 [Abyssal Hill Province Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275647664, 00275671113)
      a. Film positive b. Two profiles (C and D) covering the Abyssal Hill Province shown.
    - 0174 [Abyssal Hill Province Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Film negative b. Profiles B, C and D are shown.
    - 0175 [Scott Island Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Paper. b. Nine profiles of South Pacific Ocean area near Antarctica
    - 0176 [Scott Island Profiles A-B and C-D (#600 to #640); E-F and G-H (#555 to #560)] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
    - 0177 [Scott Island Profiles A-B and C-D (#600 to #640); E-F and G-H (#555 to #560)] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Film positive
    - 0178 [Scott Island Profile I-J, K-L, M-N O-P and Q-R] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
    - 0179 [Scott Island Profile I-J, K-L, M-N O-P and Q-R] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Film negative b. O-P and Q-R are covered by profiles #540 to #550. M-N covered by profile #590.
    - 0180 [Endeavor Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Paper. b. Covers four profiles of Macquarie Ridge, Solander Trough and the Auckland Slopes
    - 0181 [Endeavor Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671113)
      a. Film positive b. Covers four profiles of Macquarie Ridge, Solander Trough and the Auckland Slopes
    - 0182 [Abyssal Hill Province Profile Index] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
      a. Paper. b. Two profiles (A and B) covering the Continental Rise and the Abyssal Plain
    - 0183 [Abyssal Hill Province Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
      a. Film positive b. Two profiles (A and B) covering the Continental Rise and the Abyssal Plain
    - 0184 [Profile Index of the Tasman Basin, Macquarie Ridge and Solander Trough] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
      a. Paper. b. Six topographic profiles and six magnetic intensity profiles shown
    - 0185 [Profiles of the Tasman Basin, Macquarie Ridge and Solander Trough] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
      a. Film positive b. Six topographic profiles and six magnetic intensity profiles shown
    - 0186 [Profiles of the Tasman Basin, Macquarie Ridge and Solander Trough] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
      a. Film negative b. Six topographic profiles and six magnetic intensity profiles shown
    - 0187 [Profile Index for the Masca and Arica Ridges] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
    - 0188 [Index of Profiles off the West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Covers an area from 10˚ North to 60˚ South
    - 0189 [Index of Profiles off the West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275671101)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Covers an area from 10˚ North to 25˚ South and from 70˚ to 85˚ West.
    - 0190 [Miscellaneous Profile] (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
    - 0191 [Miscellaneous Profile] (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
    - 0192 [Profiles of the Lord Howe Rise, New Caledonia Basin and Norfolk Ridge] (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
    - 0193 Profiles Across South Sandwich Trench (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 40˚ North to 65˚ South and 15˚ to 40˚ West. Nine profiles showing depths in meters.
    - 0194A/K Pacific Profile (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Graph paper. b. Covers 1607S. In uncorrected fathoms, 18-21 July 1967. Sheets A- K
    - 0195 Profile Across Easter Island Ridge (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Graph paper. b. From 62˚ 53' South and 173˚ 50' East. Scale: 40:1.
    - 0196 Profile Across Clipperton Fracture Zone (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Graph paper. b. From 0˚ to 16˚ 40' North. a. Graph paper. b. From 0˚ to 16˚ 40' North. a. Graph paper. b. From 0˚ to 16˚ 40' North.
    - 0197 Profile of Ridge and Trough Province (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Graph paper. b. At 42˚ North.
    - 0198 Profile Across Cocos Ridge (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Graph paper. b. In fathoms.
    - 0199 Profile Across Cocos Ridge (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Positive print. b. From 0˚ to 5˚ North. Figure 7. Enlargement of 0198.
    - 0200 Profile of Sea Floor Between Seattle and Kodiak, Alaska (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
      a. Graph paper. b. No other identification information.
    - 0201 [Miscellaneous Profile] (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
    - 0202 [Miscellaneous Profile] (Folder Barcode: 00275671095)
    - 0203 Vema 18 Profile (Folder Barcode: 00275671010)
      a. Graph paper. b. From Wellington to Samoa. Number 12.